So even though we've been doing it in parts already.
It's good to reiterate when we're moving along and using, specifically with something that has a pattern in it or not.
You want to make sure that you are paying attention to the value tones.
I'm trying to create what looks to me as if could possible be a hand, a wrist, a fingernail, a kneecap.
I don't want to be thinking this is just a certain area for muddled color and I don't need to be paying attention to those things.
So I cut this piece out, right for the wrist here.
I'm looking at though and I'm thinking to myself, it looks nice, I like the color of it.
But I don't exactly see any shifts in value that are intriguing to me enough to show that if this is the wrist laying on top of the knee, why isn't there any value shifts inside of it?
So I may actually just lay this piece down, but begin to lay some layers over on top of it to have a little more shift in value.
Such as maybe something out of here.
I'm just going to cut out a small piece to give you an example.
This is a small piece of a darker.
So see how that would even, if I laid this over it in some area, or turned it and laid it in another area.
Its going to create a value shift.
Or give a line.
Or give a crease that much, you might try to achieve while you're doing something in drawing.
So before I lay stuff down, I actually want to kind of play with the values a little bit.